Publications, University; Collection ua950.004
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
University Publications Collection, 1921-2017
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
ua950.004
10 cubic ft.
This collection is made up of various pubilcations from the University at Albany, and groups within the institution.
Administrative History
The University at Albany has published various materials related to school, student, and faculty functions for much of its history. At times the University has directly published these materials, but more often than not these items were created by students and faculty of the institution. These materials includeed academic journals and newsletters from individual departments such as the anthropology and criminal justice dpeartments. Many of these publications did not have long runs and only encompass a few issues. The university continues to support publications from faculty and students and this collection will continue to grow in volume.
Scope and Contents
This artificial collection is made up of a variety of different publications from groups and organizations within the university. The collection includes a number of student publications, including club newsletters, smaller literary journals, independent student newspapers and humor magazines. These also include staff and faculty-produced publications such as departmental newsletters, academic journals and newsletters published both for faculty organizations such as UUP and for the community as a whole. This series also contains files produced by the university including promotional materials and mailers as well as programs for special events such as presidential inaugurations and alumni events such as mixers and reunions. There are many full runs of different publications in this collection.
Arrangement of the Collection
Collection is arranged in alphabetical order.
Acquisition Information
All items in this manuscript group were donated to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives.
Access
Access to this record group is unrestricted.
College Publications; Student publications; Scholarly publishing; Newsletters; UAlbany Reference Collections; State University of New York at Albany--Faculty
- Academic Affairs Commission Newsletter, 1966-1968; 1974 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Academic Support Programs and Services, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Academic Support Services Senior Newsletter, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- ACUSNY Association of Colleges and Universities of the State of NY, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Airwaves, 1987; 1989 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Affairs, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Affinities, 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Affirmative Action Advisor, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Affirmative Action Digest, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Albany Ahead, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Albany Almanac, 1975-1983 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Albany Asteroid, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Albany Co-Ed ACIA Intramural Athletics Newsletter, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Albany Eagle, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Albany Heritage [Planned Giving Committee], 1994 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Albany Review Superseded, 1983-1991 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Albany Sports News, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Albany Symposium on the Global Business of Semiconductors and Nanotechnology, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Alcohol Awareness Week Programs, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Alumnews, 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Alumni Association Materials, 1980-2011 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Alumni Newsletter, 1989-1994 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Alumni Weekend Brochures, 1979-2002 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- American National Theatre and Academy Region 14 Newsletter, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Artsletter, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Artsview, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Atlantis, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Authors and Editors Programs, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- BAC AT CHA Black Action Coalition Newsletter, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Bad News, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- The Banner, 1964-1965 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Basketball Programs, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Bio Club News, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Biotica, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Bits and Pieces, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Boxing Monthly: A Publication of the Albany Humor Society, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Browsing Forward Universities Libraries Newsletter (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Budget Requests, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Business Bulletin, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Byline, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Byword: Newsletter of the Writing Center, 1986-1990 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Campaign for Albany Press Release, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Campaign for Albany Brochure (1 of 2), 2003 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Campaign for Albany Brochure (2 of 2), 2003 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Campaign for the University at Albany, Undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Campus Applications of Instructional Technology, 1994 March (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Campus Christian Comment, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Campus Clipboard, 1966-1969 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Campus Clipboard, 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Campus Crusade for Christ-Albany State University, Undated (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Campus Courier Succeeds F.B.I., 1966-1969 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Campus Courier, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Campus Environmental Improvement Program, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Campus Master Plan Update Guide, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Campus Voice Communications Workers of America, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Capital District Humanities Program, Undated (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Capital District Writing Project Newsletter, 1981-1982; 1986 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Career Newsletter, 1971-1980 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Career Newsletter, 1981-1984 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Career Newsletter, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Caribbean Studies Newsletter, 1991-1993 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Carte Blanche: The Undergraduate Journal College of Humanities and Fine Arts, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Catalyst, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- CCD Newsletter, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- CCI Times, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Celac Reports Center for Latin American & the Caribbean, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Center for Advanced Thin Film Technology Investment Request and Promotional Materials, 1993-1997 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Center for the Arts & Humanities Newsletter, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- The Center for the Arts and Humanities:, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Center for Environmental Sciences and Technology Management Prospectus, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Center for Inter-American Studies Publications, Undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Center for Technology in Government Publications, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Center for Women in Government Publications, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- CEP Newsletter, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- " The Challenge and the Choice", 1988 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Chemistry Newsletter, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Chinese Student Association Monthly Newsletter, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Chronica, 1967-1973 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Chronica, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Chronica, 1976-1978 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Chronica, 1979-1981 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Class Newsletter Alumni Association, 1927-1980 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Clinic News, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Clio- The History Journal of the Chi Delta Chapter of Phi Alpha Theta, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Cohen, Laura, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- College of Arts and Sciences Newsletter and Fliers, 2002-2010; Undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
- College of Continuing Studies Gazette, 1982-1985 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- College of Humanities and Fine Arts Newsletter, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- College of Nanoscale Engineering News Releases, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Columns, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Comity, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Communications Newsletter, 1985-1988 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Community Rights and Responsibilities Guide, 1993-2001 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Community Service and Post-Secondary Continuing Education Fiscal Years, 1966-1973; 1974 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Compact Connections, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Computer Access Report, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Computing and Networking Services, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Computing Center Publications, 1980-1998 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Computing Center Newsletter, 1968-1970 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Computing Services News, 1990/1991 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- The Conjufator, 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Connections (School of Business Publications), 1997-2006 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Consensus, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Constitution of the New York State Teacher's Association, 1913 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- The Contact: Undergraduate Political Science Advisor, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Continue!, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Controversy, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Counterpoint, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Course of Study and Syllabus for the College Graduate Certifications, 1922 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- CPE Agenda, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Creating After Teaching: Three Facility Emeriti, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Criminal Justice Education, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Crisis Bulletin, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Cue Associate, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Cypriot Flame, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 55)
- Dane Digest, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Data Channel, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 57)
- Department of History Newsletter, 1983-1984; 1987 (Box 2, Folder 58)
- Department of Mathematics Newsletter, 1980-1987 (Box 2, Folder 59)
- Department of Music Files, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 60)
- Department of Physics Newsletters, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 61)
- The Discourse Record (LSSA Newsletter), 1970 (Box 2, Folder 62)
- Dippikill Promotional Materials, Undated (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Directions- School of Education, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Disability Needs Assessment, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 65)
- Division for Continuing Studies Brochures and Publications, 1982-1985 (Box 2, Folder 66)
- Division of Student Affairs Publications, 2000; Undated (Box 2, Folder 67)
- Doc Digest, 1976-1979 (Box 2, Folder 68)
- The Doclet, 1983-1985 (Box 2, Folder 69)
- Downtown, 1983-1985 (Box 2, Folder 70)
- Draft of Environmental Impact Statement for Capital Project Plan, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- EAP: The Newsletter, 1984-1994; 1996-1998; 2000-2001; 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- East Greenbush Campus Brochures, Undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Education Bulletin, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Educational Opportunities Program Newsletter, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Educational Opportunities Program Newsletter, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Educational Opportunities Program Brochures, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Educator, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Emerging Issues, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Emphasis/Albany & Emphasis/State University of New York at Albany, 1969-1973 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Employee Assistance Program Publications, 1990-2009 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Enlaces Latinos, 2006-2007 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Environmental Issues, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Estate and Financial Planning Techniques, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Eta Phi Alumne Bulletin, 1942; Undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Evaluation Consortium at Albany News Update, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- The Explorer, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- "Eye on the Universe" Television Course, Undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Factbooks and Promotional Materials, 1979-2001 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Factbook, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Facility Association Newsletter, 1959-1964 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Facility Perspectives: Sharing Ideas on Assessment, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Faculty Publications and Creative Activities, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Faculty Publications and Creative Activities, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Faculty Association News, 1965-1969 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Faculty Senate, 1990-1999 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- FDR Centennial Celebration Program, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Finance and Business, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Financial Aid Brochure, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Five Quad Ambulance Brochure, Undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Focus: The Magazine for Albany State, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Focus (Office of Community Relations), 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Focus on Africa, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Focus on Reading, 1971-1976 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Focus On Teaching, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Football Programs and Media Guides, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Fore Word, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Forerunner, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Forerunner, 1975-1977 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Forerunner, 1978-1981 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- For the Parent, 1982-1988 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- For the Record, 1991-1993 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Forget Me Not, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Forum, 1994-1998 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Freshman Forecast, 1977-1978; 1988 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Fuerza Latina, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Galpin Society Journal, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Gateways to the Past, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Gazette, 1989-1994 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Gemini Library Catalog Manual, Undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
- General Studies Gazette, 1976-1990 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Getting off, 1977-1981 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Glance at Some Distinguished Alumni, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Global Synergies, 2015-2016 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Gnomes News, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Goals of Higher Education Interdependent World Program, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Graduate Newsletter, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Graduate School of Public Affairs Newsletter, 1962-1965 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- Graduate Student News, 1992-1996 (Box 3, Folder 50)
- Graduate Study Publications, 1984-1995 (Box 3, Folder 51)
- Graffiti, Undated (Box 3, Folder 52)
- Grapevine, 1975-1976; 1984 (Box 3, Folder 53)
- Grapevine (Minority Student Services), 1983-1986 (Box 3, Folder 54)
- Grass Roots (SUNYA), 1972 (Box 3, Folder 55)
- Gremlin Gazette, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 56)
- Gremlin Growler, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 57)
- Habari- Newsletter of the Department of African and Afro-American Studies, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 58)
- Helderberg Review, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 59)
- Helderberg Review, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 60)
- Highlights, 1976-1978 (Box 3, Folder 61)
- Hispanism as Humanism Symposium, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 62)
- History Department Publications, 1968-2003 (Box 3, Folder 63)
- Hokum: SUNY Albany's Humor Magazine, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Honor Roll Donors, 2004-2005 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- The Hormone (Chemistry Club), 1921 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Hotline, 1971-1976 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Hotline, 1977-1984 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Hotline, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Humor Research Newsletter, 1976-1978 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- IEA Newsletter, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- IFAI (International Fire Administration Institute), 1970-1972 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- IFC Rush Preview, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- IMS Newsletter, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Initiatives for Women, 1995-1999 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Inferno, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Innovations Newsletters, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Insight, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Institute of Gerontology, 1979-1981 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Institutional Research Publications, Undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Interface, 1974-1975; 1979 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- International Student Office Notes, 1966-1977 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Interviews, 1987-1993 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- In Touch, 1983-1986 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Intramural Update, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- IRIS (Institute for Renaissance Interdisciplinary Studies), 1980-1984 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- IROW News, 1988-1993 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- ISA Outlook, 1969-1971 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- ITS News, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Jay's Journal, 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- JHS Report, 1956-1962 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Journal of Continuing Social Work Education, 1981-1983 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Journal of Continuing Social Work Education, 1983-1986 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Journal of Continuing Social Work Education, 1986-1990 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Journal of Undergraduate Research, 1988-1993 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Judaic Studies (Dept. of Judaic Studies, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Karen Hitchcock Inauguration Folder Materials, 1995-2004 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Kick in the ASP, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Kujichagulia, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Knowledge (School of Education Quarterly), 2003-2007 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- L' Humaniste (Vol.1), 1967 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- L' Humaniste (Vol.2), 1967-1968 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- L' Humaniste (Vol.3), 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- L' Humaniste (Vol.4), 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- LACS News, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Latino Journal, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Leadership Bulletin (UUP), 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- The Librarian's Newsletter, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Library Faculty Minutes, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Library Issues, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Library Liberation, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Library Perspectives, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- LSSA News, 1971-1973 (Box 4, Folder 45)
- Living off Campus, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Lorelei, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 47)
- Major Decisions, Undated (Box 4, Folder 48)
- Marcia Brown Research Room Dedication Programs, 1997-2001 (Box 4, Folder 49)
- Martin Luther King Jr. Luncheon Program, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 50)
- Mass Media/Adult, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Master's Theses: A Bibliography, 1914-1978 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Memorial Programs and Cards, 1990-2008 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Message from Finance and Business, 1985-1991 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Microelectronics New York: A Strategic Paradigm for the 21st Century, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Microscope, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Mission, Priorities and Programs for Action, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- The Monitor, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Momentum, 1992-1995 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Much Ado About, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Mumford Chronicles, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Mural and Stained Glass Window Descriptions, Undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Nadir (Annual Literacy Journal Funded by the Student Association), 1981; 1984; 1987 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Networking, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- New York Folklore Quarterly, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- New York State College for Teachers Bulletin Vol.1 No 1, 1915 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- The Newmanite, 1961-1966 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- News Analysis, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- News and Views, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- News from Phi Delta, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- News on Women in Government, 1978-1990 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- News Summer Review, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- The News: State University of New York (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Noteworthy News- From the Office for Research, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- NY SUNY 2020 Challenge Grant, 2012 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- N.Y.S Council on Economic Education Newsletter, 1967-1969 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- NYPIRD News, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- NYSAIAW News, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- OASIS Catalogs, 2003-2008 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- The Objector, 1967-1968 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Off Campus, Undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Off Campus Community Newsletter, 1975-1977 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Office of Academic Support Publications, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Office of the President Publications, 1968-2002 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Office of Residential Life Promotional Materials, 2000; Undated (Box 5, Folder 33)
- On Campus- A Planning Guide, 1974-1978 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- "100 Women of Excellence" Women's Business Council, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Opening Celebration for the Life of Sciences Research Building, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Opening Days Newsletter, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Oracle, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- ORS Newsletter, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Out of the Sandbox, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Outlook (Disabled Student Services), 1980-1985 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Overseas Chinese Life Scientists Association Newsletter, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Paintings and Sculptures from the Nelson A. Rockefeller Collection, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 43)
- PA' Lante, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 44)
- Partnerships: The University at Albany and the Schools, Undated (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Patroon Room Recorder, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 46)
- Penguin, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 47)
- Performing Arts Center Materials, 1990-2013 (Box 5, Folder 48)
- Personnel/ Human Resources Division News, 1977-1992 (Box 5, Folder 49)
- Personnel Notes, 1987-2003 (Box 5, Folder 50)
- Perspectives (Department of French Newsletter), 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 51)
- Petr kotik Residency Flier, 2009 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Phi Beta Kappa Publications, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 52)
- Philosophical Information Bulletin- PHIB, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 53)
- Philosophical Information Bulletin- PHIB, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 54)
- Phobia and Anxiety Disorders Clinic Newsletter, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 55)
- Placement Manual, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 56)
- Pocket Events Guides, 2003-2012 (Box 5, Folder 57)
- "Preferable Future for SUNY and the State" Senate Report, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 58)
- Presidential Reports, 1990-2006 (Box 5, Folder 59)
- President's Award for Leadership Program, 2017 (Box 5, Folder 60)
- President's Task Force on Priorities and Resources Section II- Academic Program Recommendations, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 61)
- The Pretzel, 1924 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Private Giving Reports, 1978-1990 (Box 5, Folder 62)
- Proceedings of the 1992 Edward F. Kelly Evaluation Conference (Box 5, Folder 63)
- Professional Communications Libraries, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Professional Developments, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- The Professor, 1967-1970 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Project Excell Promotional Materials Publications, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Project Renaissance Flier, Undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Proposal for Program Management Services for Nanotronics 300, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- The Public Affair, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Public Health Memo, 1986-1997 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Quarterly Report, 1992-1998 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Radiation Effects in Semiconductors Conference Programs, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Radish, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Rainbow Connector, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- R.C # 37 Newsletter, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Recommended Model for EOP, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Record of Research and Activity, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- R.E.D Line, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Redoubt, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Reference News, 1991-1994 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Reflections (Department of Educational Administration and Policy Studies Newsletter), 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Representation and Electoral Systems, 1991-2006 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Re Reading, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Re Reading, 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Research and Publications Newsletter, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Research at Albany, 2001-2013 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Research Directory, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Research Foundation Decennial Report, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Research from the School of Education, 2007-2013 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Research Evaluation Newsletter, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Research: State University of New York, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Researcher, 1977-1979 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Research Foundation- Enabling Discovery Annual Report, 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Resnet Operating Manual, Undated (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Newsletter of the World of Criminal Justice Library Network, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Residential Life Calendar, 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Returning Older Students Newsletter, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- RF Personnel News, 1983-1985 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Right Alternative, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Rockefeller Archive Center Newsletter, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Rockefeller College Brochures, 1989-1998 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Rockefeller College Programs and Promotional Materials, 1983-2008 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Rockefeller College Report, 1984-1991 (Box 6, Folder 40)
- RSVP Messenger, 1982-1991 (Box 6, Folder 41)
- RSVP Messenger, 1991-1994 (Box 6, Folder 42)
- Satan's Scroll (Class of 1965), 1961 (Box 6, Folder 43)
- Sayles International Newsletter, 1974-1977 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- S/C Action Letter, 1985-1991 (Box 6, Folder 44)
- School of Business, University at Albany, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 45)
- School of Business Newsletter, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 46)